Visit turkision.com for more!
The Atranos Castle has been surrounded!
That dog called Imren, show yourself!
This is our last warning!
You have until sunset!
You will hand over the Castle Atranos!
And you will seek our
forgiveness for the things you did.
If you do not leave the castle,
then you will face our wrath!
Who will do that, you?
With how many alps are you
going to get over these walls?
The number of alps is not
the one that conquers castles.
We fight with our hearts!
You will learn the truth when
these walls crumble upon you!
However, it will be late for you by then!
Tell Osman, I will have each
and every one of your heads..
..just as I did Bayindir Bey and his alps.
Atranos will be your last siege!
We came with peace.
We wanted you to surrender.
However, if you do not surrender, then..
..you will die hanging from this yard.
Then I will make you remember
your words, Imren Tegin!
Will Imren Tegin leave the castle to Gunduz Bey?
I know that he won't without fighting.
That is why..
I sent him to Atranos..
..to confuse Imren Tegin.
Whatever his response will
be, it won't change the outcome.
Atranos will be ours in the end.
We will have Bayindir Bey's vengeance as well.
No. States do not take revenge.
They only provide justice.
We will do so as well. However, Imren Tegin..
..will think that Gunduz Bey
came to Atranos for vengeance.
That is why his duty is at Atranos.
We will not take Atranos for vengeance.
We will not even take Atranos for now.
Because, as long as Kite is here..
..it is impossible to take Atranos.
Because the soldiers coming from Bursa and Iznik..
..can arrive at Atranos through Kite.
That is why Kite..
..is a very important location.
Not only Atranos..
..but Bursa and Iznik conquests are
not possible without taking Kite first.
Unless we have our banner
at Kite, we can not move.
We will have our banner.
If Allah permits, we will have our banner.
They will think that we will have Atranos first.
Howeveri we will walk to Kite first.
My Bey, this Imren Tegin will assign
a commander of his called "Levi".
I've asked around. They say he is a clever man.
They say they used to fight together.
He is skilled in sword they say.
My Bey, forgive me but..
..how will Kite fall..
..when all the alps and weapons are at Atranos?
Kite..
Kite is under siege for a long time already.
You did wrong by killing Bayindir.
-Relax.
-Don't tell me to relax.
-Osman's armies are on our gates.
-I wanted this.
They were just overhasty.
What do you mean you wanted this?
I killed Bayindir for Osman to siege Atranos.
Now listen to me carefully,
Olivia. You will go to Osman.
Osman would kill me.
You will act as if you escaped the siege.
You will take your niece with you.
Since Osman's son loves your niece..
..we will use her.
From what I've heard..
..they will marry Osman's son
and Gunduz daughter to unite Kayis.
That can not happen, Olivia.
How can I prevent this?
A loving man does not marry
with just his father's request.
Your niece will ensure this.
And you will earn their trust.
It is not possible for me to earn their trust.
They will trust you.
You will tell them that I've killed
Bayindir to lay siege upon Atranos.
When Osman comes to me with all of his forces..
..then he will face my surprise.
I will disrupt their palace so much..
..that they won't even notice their end is near.
We will send them away from these lands.
And how will you handle the siege?
Osman does not know about
the secret passages in Atranos.
I will use those passages. While
he thinks he has me surrounded..
..I will cut his veins one by one.
Which means, I am the one surrounding
him. He just doesn't know about it.
Our encampment is ready, near the Castle Kite.
Alps are waiting to attack for a while.
Uraz Bey. You will take position here.
As you command, my Bey. Alaeddin Bey..
My Bey.
The siege of Atranos is on your shoulders..
..until Konur Bey comes back from his duty.
As you command, my Bey.
The rest of the beys will be under your command.
-As you command, my Bey.
-Thank you. Malhun hatun..
You and Elcim Hatun will
welcome Gunduz Bey's people.
I will send the ones
that can hold a sword to
the barracks and the
rest will go into the city.
Okay, okay.
Bala Hatun, you will stand back with Baciyans.
You are my secret swords.
We will stand ready, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Now, it is time for Imren Tegin.
He will think we will attack Atranos.
However, with the alps of Gunduz
Bey and those from the barracks..
..we will surround Kite.
This way, they will be divided.
Soldiers won't be able to pass through here.
Then, we will already have Atranos surrounded.
And we will make the killer of Bayindir Bey pay.
If Allah permits.
Atranos will be a grave to them,
and a treasure to us, my Bey.
However, first Kite.
It is. We will not be done with Kite only.
We got a message from Karesi port too. Many
Crusaders are marching towards us from there.
For this reason, Orhan Bey
and Konur Bey went to the port.
If Allah permits, they'll be back with good news.
-If Allah permits., my Bey.
-If Allah permits..
We thought we got rid of Tajeddin.
Now we have got a new trouble.
He's also calling all the jackals from the west.
Jackals can bite nobody in our land, Elcim Hatun.
Because Osman Bey is always standing.
Names change. Faces change.
But the fight never changes.
This is the fight between the right and
the wrong. They can try whatever they want.
We will be victorious with Allah's will.
If everyone performs their duties properly,
Kite will be ours.
Atranos will be ours.
And Imren Tegin's head will be ours.
No worries. Allah is the only Victorious.
Allah is the only Victorious.
Dastards. Those hatuns are Turkish, my Shahzade.
They started doing evil
things as soon as they arrived.
Osman Bey was right.
Heathens are getting united.
They came to Karesi by the sea from the west.
We will find out why these
dastards came here, Konur Bey.
We have a duty.
But we don't have any duties more
important than protecting our people.
We are outnumbered.
First, we will find out...
...where they are taking those hatuns.
Varangians, come on! We're going ahead to scout!
Wolves hunt whoever leaves the herd.
Now we will see what they intend to do. Let's go.
In the war, those who
predict the enemy's moves win.
You are attacking to die!
Daniel.
A swords sometimes cuts the enemy
and sometimes becomes a shield.
You need to learn how to defend before you attack.
Your soldiers will be as strong as my men.
Or they are going to die.
These are the tax coins
collected to be delivered to Osman.
Two chests to soldiers and one to Imren Tegin.
Poor guys... They think they can
get rid of Osman with these gold coins.
Hand out my share to my brave fighters.
Long live Imren Tegin! Long live
Imren'Tegin! Long live Imren Tegin!
-Everything is set, Imreh Tegin.
-Good.
We will be careful.
With the newcomer soldiers,
...you will protect the castle
of Kite at the cost of your life.
Reinforcements are on the way. Treat them well.
-As you wish. I will train them.
-I know.
So your gift is on the way too. I'm
getting nice women brought for you.
Stop there. Where are you going?
I need you alive, not dead.
Tie this dog up. He knows things to tell us.
Come on.
I knew Imren wouldn't
give away Atranos without a
fight. But I wanted him to
be sure about our move.
So I wanted you to see the situation.
Imren's soldiers are on alert and they are sharp.
Our men are on the way and they are tired.
They are, but we can beat their sharp ones easily.
Walls cannot protect them.
You trusted beys and warriors for Atranos.
Now let's talk about our part.
-How will we hunt?
-Come with me.
Alps have been watching Kite for a long time.
Everybody knows well what to do.
We know where to attack
with catapults. We will split up.
While one wing hits the walls,
...the other wing will climb up the towers.
-It will be hard.
-Good. Good.
Let it be hard, Osman Bey. If it
were easy, it wouldn't be a homeland.
You say so, huh? Then Kite...
...which we take with blood and right of sword...
...shall be your property.
Thank you, Osman. Now you've
increased my desire to fight!
Your alps will be exhausted.
Kayi soldiers cannot be broken by exhaustion...
...but by laziness, Osman Bey. Don't worry.
-They will fight like lions, if Allah permits.
-For sure.
-Yes, my Bey? You wanted to see me.
-Son.
You'll go to the frontier market
before the conquest of Atranos.
Go talk to Mehmed.
Tell him we'll take Atranos. Don't
tell him the truth. I don't trust him.
-But, my Bey...
-Son.
I'm sending you there deliberately.
You'll end the hostility between you two.
Be sure whether they will back us up or
not if we face some troubles in the fight.
As you order, my Bey.
Well, Gunduz Bey... Let's go see the headquarters.
-Boran, bring the horses.
-Alright, my Bey.
Mother... Mother.
Mother.
I know you miss your mother.
But they became martyrs for
our homeland and our holy cause.
So we need to fight for our
cause for the sake of them.
We won't bow against anyone.
We will live for the future
of Turks in Allah's path.
You will grow up and fight for the Islam world.
You will have many victories.
Now wipe your tears.
Those who did this to us will cry. We won't.
See? Your brothers are there.
Take these.
Here. Go give them.
If your mother were alive,
she would be proud of you.
May Allah make her soul rest in peace.
I've been watching you.
I see how you are looking after your people.
You're behaving like a true Bey's
daughter with your mind and strength.
If you see something good in
me, I took it from my parents.
My mother told us the battles of
our ancestors instead of lullabies.
We used to close our eyes for a dream.
Red Apple... The words of Allah...
I hope our dream will be the fate of our kin.
Migration, fight, martyrdom and
longing... They are all from Him.
Praise be to you!
You're just from the blood of Mother Hayme.
Praise be, daughter!
I want it to happen, but...
...I don't know if Orhan and
you are the fate of each other.
But I'm sure of this.
The house you are in will always be in peace.
The man you'll marry and your
children-to-be-born are so lucky.
May you always have a good luck and fate, dear.
If Allah permits, it will be
good for both of the tribes.
If Allah permits.
Speak... Are you serving Imren Tegin?
Where are you going?
We are going
to the Kite Castle.
The ones who are on the way will go to Kite.
That castle is really important for Imren
Tegin. We are going there to support them.
Of course you know...
Before taking Kite Castle...
...you cannot conquer the other ones.
Who else will come? Tell me.
All mercenaries in Byzantium will come. Just wait.
-Just mercenaries?
-No.
The emperor released all the prisoners in
his lands in exchange for their fighting.
They will unite with Templars, Varangians...
...and come here with hundreds of ships.
Look at my face. What made the Emperor so angry?
That Bey named Osman killed Princess Maria.
Thus, Emperor gave all
his soldiers to Imren Tegin.
We are just the advance force.
-What about captive Turk women?
-They are just for entertainment.
It must be entertaining now.
Get ready. Come on.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
So Osman Bey is surrounding Atranos, huh?
But he didn't even invite us to the council.
-How was the council Uraz Bey?
-It was alright, Mehmet Bey.
Osman Bey says that we should unite
because of the issue about Imren Tegin.
And... as you know, Atranos.
I know. Osman Bey will
show the power of Turks to...
...infidels by taking Atranos, huh?
But fortunately, we are not
Osman Bey's enemies, Mehmet Bey.
His mind works differently.
Do you think Osman Bey is planning a new game?
No... I am not saying that.
I should go, if you allow me, Mehmet Bey..
-Thank you.
Osman!
Osman does not trust us, Kanyumaz.
-You are right, my Bey.
-He set up the council against Imren.
And he warned Beys against Imren.
Osman must have another plan other than Atranos.
No one will know that Uraz Bey came here
and what was talked about here, Kanyumaz.
-Yes my Bey.
-Go now.
OSMAN BEY KITE HEADQUARTERS
What is the situation? Tell me. I want
the preparations to be done until tomorrow.
It will be done, my Bey.
Alps, come on, do not stop!
You can even break the greatest
walls with these catapults, Osman Bey.
Yes... But catapults won't be
enough, we will also dig beneath them.
What is your plan, Osman Bey?
Are the passages ready? How is it going?
Alps are digging day and night, my Bey.
If Allah permits, we will be
in the scorpion's nest before morning.
I don't want a single mistake.
There won't be an accident
with Allah's consent, my Bey.
As you ordered, we will have
everything done if Allah permits.
Inform Alps. They have to be careful.
Look, they are not like the other ones.
You will follow us from behind, Aykurt.
Yes my Bey. -So...
...you are also digging a tunnel
to get in the castle, Osman Bey.
We are digging with our hands, Gunduz
Bey. We are digging with our hands.
I will hurt that Imren dog so badly that...
..he won't be able to breathe.
Alaeddin Bey.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you hear my brother? If he sees you here...
-He can't do anything.
I came here with the order of Osman Bey.
Good.
I didn't think you came here for another reason.
Alaeddin!
Mehmet Bey... I brought news from Osman Bey.
He wants to talk to you.
Good then. Come to my tent.
Gonca. Come with us.
Tell me Alaeddin Bey. What does Osman Bey want?
Osman Bey surrounded Atranos
castle. Now we want to know.
Will you stand by our side when the
time comes, or will you stand against us?
Osman Bey set up a council.
Why didn't he invite us?
Osman Bey's own Beys were present at the council.
Did you come under our command
to be present in our council?
You are our ally Germiyan.
Now I want to hear your answer.
Are you still our ally...
...or will you not support
Turks while they struggle?
Alaeddin Bey.
Our issue with you is different...
...and the issue of the state is different.
I will come whenever Osman Bey calls.
But... I will also ask for something.
The path to strength lies in
knowing every move of your opponent.
If you know, you can defeat them and be strong.
You will know every move of Osman.
You want me to be your spy.
I won't betray a Turk.
I don't want you to be my spy.
Just don't stand against us and disrupt our trade.
Besides, you still have to know
Osman's moves for your trades.
After what happened, Yenisehir's
doors are closed to Germiyan.
-I cannot approach them.
-You will.
What is on your mind?
You will trade
with Osman again.
This will let you approach them.
We will trade in Yenisehir again. We
will have a counter at the marketplace.
Good. I will inform Osman
Bey about this, Mehmet Bey.
-Now, excuse me.
-Sure. -Thank you.
Gonca! Stop.
Were you serious about what you said?
I was, my Gonca. Osman Bey is in a great war.
We will do what suits us, Germiyan.
We will stand behind Osman
Bey. We cannot be enemies now.
What changed in two days?
-I owe Osman Bey.
I don't like owing to someone.
My Shahzade.
Mehmet approached me in a
friendly manner and reached his hand.
But he is not a man who can do this.
-Did something different happen?
-Nothing happened, my Shahzade.
Keep your eyes on him. Learn if there is...
...something different behind this.
-Don't worry.
Put it on your arm.
It will heal you.
Ghazi Alp sent it.
He wants his father to
recover as soon as possible.
So my valiant is worried about his father huh?
-Thank you my Shahzade.
-Thnak you.
Safely.
All the warriors from the west
are coming here in crowds.
Prisoners waiting to be killed,outlaws...
...templars, knights.
Don't forget the Catalans,
Imren Tegin. They will...
...all be under your command as a massive army.
-Never.
How many times did they stand
against Osman with their armies?
Mongols, Byzantines, how many times?
Which one defeated them in that field?
There won't be an army. Turks unite
very quickly when they face common enemy.
We will eat Osman's flesh by blowing like a mouse.
We will poison the waters,
we will burn the fields.
We will attack the caravans,
we will make animals sick.
We will make sure people
cannot trust each other. Then...
...Osman's head will fall!
Welcome, Kanyumaz.
I knew you would find right path in the end.
So, what news did you bring?
I know, you are having a rough time.
You think you are betraying a Bey of Turks.
However, I am a Turk as well.
Beys also draw their swords against each other.
Do not worry, I will not forget
about you when I have these lands.
I will not forget about your family as
well. So you best not forget about it too.
Hatun, do not worry.
I will save you from here.
Hold on a little longer.
Do you still object, Kanyumaz?
-I will make you pay for...
-Ssshhh.
Your hatun and your child
are the only ones to pay a price.
You will tell me everything
between Mehmed and Osman.
If you do not, you don't
want to know what I will do.
Now tell me, what news did you bring?
Mehmed Bey..
..thinks that Atranos is
not Osman's primary target.
So Osman makes another move other than Atranos.
Imren Tegin, now give me back my family.
Do not worry. I will take care of your family.
I will be done with you when Osman dies.
-Take him.
-Imren Tegin..
I killed Bayindir to bring
Osman at the doors of Atranos.
We would've brought soldiers
when he came through Kite..
..and escape through castle's secret passages.
What changed?
It seems Osman figured out my plan.
He won't be threatened from all sides.
He will walk to Kite first.
There must be a secret encampment nearby.
Search for it. We will paint
that encampment with blood.
Holofira, we are going away
from here. Andrea, pack up.
What is it, aunt? Why?
Imren Tegin will kill us.
It is our turn after the lords,
I've heard it with my own ears.
Aunt, the castle is under
siege. How will we get out?
Even if we do, where will we go?
-To Osman Bey.
-What do you mean to Osman Bey?
I will befriend the enemy of my enemy.
Only he can help us.
No one can kill Imren Tegin but Osman.
Everything's all set, my lady.
I will get you out, however..
However what?
Our only^way out is the hole
where we throw out garbage.
We have to do this.
We don't have any other option to get
rid of Imren Tegin, come on we leave.
Come on.
We saw them digging a
tunnel towards the Castle Kite.
I will disrupt all of your plans, Osman.
My valiant.
My valiant..
No.
My valiants..
My alps..
Cerkutay, Boran.
Orhan.. Konur!
My sons..
Orhan.. Alaeddin..
Orhan! Alaeddin!
The State of Osman..
My Osman?
Osman? My Bey?
My Bey, what happened?
-Are you alright?
-Bala..
I am alright.
I saw a dream..
..my sons..
..my alps..
..this is hard.
It was very hard.
The challenge of such a blessed
road will be hard, my Osman.
You decided walk knowing that, right?
It will be tough.
But I can see the end.
The end will be good for us.
The end will be good. Look.
My children are in our house.
With our fellows,
...we will achieve our goal. We will. We will.
Our dream will come true.
If Allah permits, my Osman.
If Allah permits.
We will walk in this path as long as we can.
Yes, we will. We will walk.
-Were you going to say something?
-Orhan and the others are waiting for you.
Let's go then. Come on.
Fatma, are you cooking
halvah? I could have made it.
I'm making it for my brothers, Ulgen Hatun.
You know, both of them are broken-hearted.
-This mat sweeten their mouths.
-Well thought.
Maybe, Shahzade Alaaddin and
Gonca Hatun will come together, huh?
No! That tall Shahzade will never...
Alright, you will marry Gonca. What was I saying?
They may come together. Don't
be upset. There he bites again!
Even if you silence me,
you can't silence my heart!
You hid Gonca Hatun as you were jealous,
right? I won't talk to you anymore!
-Alright, Ghazi. Ghazi!
-My Allah...
-I throw or you run?
-No! No!
Sister Ulgen, do you know
something about Gonca Hatun?
You really think she and my brother
will make peace after all what happened?
I don't know.
But I can see they still love each other.
It's love, Fatma. You can't
put out that fire so easily.
I agree, but my brother Orhan...
I don't know what he'll do.
Even if Orhan says yes...
I don't want to think about what will happen...
...when Holofira hears
about Orhan and Elcim Hatun.
She will be ruined. Pity.
I feel sorry for them.
Holofira.
Catalans, Varangians... Emperor
released even the prisoners.
He's sending them to our lands in good numbers.
They're coming in waves to fight us, my Bey.
He promised some of them booties
and sent some to fight for Cross.
But after all, they are coming to take Isabel.
-Where are they going?
-To the castle of Kite, my Bey.
Kite is the most available place
for raiding and looting, my Bey.
If they deploy there, they
will start raiding around.
And the Mongolian trouble will go on.
If we don't break Imren Tegin,
we'll stay between two fires.
The latest information shows us...
...how important the conquest of Kite is.
If the looters Shahzade Orhan mentioned come,
...things will be harder for us, Osman Bey.
We won't let them, Gunduz Bey. We
will have captured Kite before they arrive.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in!
My Bey, they attacked the headquarter of Kite.
What?
Imren Tegin raided suddenly and
they burned everything down, my Bey.
Imren Tegin, huh?
Imren Tegin... Is that so?
We will see. We will see.
Gunduz Bey.
What is happening?
Tell me. We won't fall into despair just
because they attacked the headquarter, will we?
Bala Hatun. Malhun Hatun.
We won't vanish even if they break us! My sons.
Orhan! Alaaddin!
Shh... Don't! Don't!
We...
...are the Ummah of Rasulullah (PBUH)
who got over every hardship he experienced.
If they hit our headquarters, of course
we will make them pay for it heavily.
If they killed our Bey dastardly,
we will behead a hundred lords!
If they attack us with an army...
...we will crush them with our horses.
We will take Kite tomorrow. Get ready.
-At this time, Osman Bey?
-At this time!
Now they will not think that we
will attack. That's why we will attack.
Bala Hatun... They are not aware of the
sisters we have been preparing secretly.
Now it's time. You have the key of the castle.
The Turkish woman standing behind her man...
...is ready to drink the sherbet of shahada
before her man, my Bey. Don't worry.
Thank you. They will all see tomorrow.
-Boran!
-My Bey!
Send news to that Imren Tegin.
I will talk to him one on one near Atranos.
Yes my Bey.
We will see.
Long live Imren Tegin!
All the executioners of the west are here!
Your swords will be covered in
blood, your bags will be filled with gold!
We will make history in these lands!
Those who can gather them around
a table can make history as well!
Long live Imren Tegin!
Soon, the siege of Atranos will be removed.
Osman's failure to consider
the passages cost him dearly.
Now... I have gifts for you. Bring them!
I brought these women through
the secret passage for you!
I will raise their children
and make them my warriors!
Take them!
I am the grandson of Keykavus
from the Seljuk lineage.
An arrow I shoot towards the
west will return to me as an army.
Both Turkish and Byzantine blood flow in my veins.
I am Imren Tegin.
I will be the only ruler of Roman Empire!
Long live Imren Tegin!
We will take this right together, my siblings.
I will establish a kingdom.
I will take Osman's lands...
...and establish a kingdom
which will unite both sides.
A kingdom where only
the powerful's desires are fulfilled...
...where only the sword and courage are respected.
Here, great prices will be paid, and
they will be paid back with interest!
When the kingdom under my rule is established...
...the Catalans will govern their own seats.
The Varangians will be able to...
...take their ships and set sail whenever
they want, just like in the old days!
The Templars will be able to find as
many weapons and horses as they desire!
You will serve me!
I will make your dreams come true!
Long live Imren Tegin!
Imren Tegin... Osman sent
news. He wants to talk to you.
He couldn't defeat us, he must
have decided to kiss our hand.
Osman wants to see me to kneel before me!
Tell him... I will see him.
One day, we will also celebrate the victory
of taking Osman's head at this table.
Enjoy!
Come! Come!
Allah Almighty speaks the truth. My Allah...
I seek refuge in You alone and
ask for Your mercy. Grant me...
...and my children the victory
of defeating the infidels...
...and raising the sanjak of
Islam throughout the world.
O my Allah, may You reward
our martyrs whose blood...
...watered our land with Your jannah.
Make them neighbors to our
Prophet Efendi (PBUH), my Allah.
Allow us to take the revenge of
our martyrs, my Allah. Aameen.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in.
My Bey, as you ordered, we
found the houses of our martyrs.
Okay. Fulfill their needs.
They are the entrustments of our
valiants. We will always embrace them.
Yes my Bey.
My Orhan... I don't want to stress you.
I know how hard it is for you, but..
...everyone expects you to make a decision.
Elcim said she will obey her father.
What will be your decision?
Mother... You know what my heart says.
I love Holofira.
-I know, my son... I know, but...
-But, for the well-being of the state...
...you want me to marry Elcim Hatun, right?
Mother, you never wanted Holofira.
Believe me, my heart is
also in pain, just like yours.
You are my child.
But that's what I've been trying
to tell you from the beginning...
-It's about the state!
-I know, mother.
I know, it's about the state.
Let's assume that I said yes, gave up on
myself and accepted to marry Elcim Hatun.
What about Holofira?
What will happen to her, mother?
While I love Holofira for all these years..
..how will I tell her this?
How will I say, "I will marry another hatun"?
Allah gives the challenge to
those who can handle it, they say.
You are strong enough to
overcome this challenge, Orhan.
You will do the right thing, for our future.
Are we allowed, Malhun Hatun?
Come in.
Ulgen Hatun sends word.
Holofira and her aunt has come.
-They are coming here.
-What?
-Who are these hatuns?
-This is..
..this is her. The lover of Shahzade Orhan.
The daughter of lord.
What are you doing here
while Atranos is under siege?
Olivia Hatun, are you here to beg?
Never. I never beg to anyone, Malhun Hatun.
I wouldn't be here if I didn't have to.
Your soldiers at Atranos are in danger.
-What do you mean?
-Imren Tegin has a great plan.
When he killed Bayindir Bey,
he knew you would siege Atranos.
Now, he will attack your alps.
Why would you do such a favor to us?
Because Holofira and I are in danger.
All the commanders at the castle
are under the rule of Imren Tegin.
I had no choice but to take shelter
to you in order to protect Holofira.
Olivia Hatun. Do not worry, you are safe here.
However, what I don't understand is,
why does Imren Tegin wants to kill you?
As we know, Imren Tegin is here
because of a letter sent to The Emperor.
Imren Tegin says that The
Emperor supports him, however..
..I don't think
Emperor trusts him.
Imren killed all the lords.
If we didn't escape, he
would've killed us as well.
Alright then. Ulgen..
..take Olivia Hatun and Holofira
to a safe house in Yenisehir.
I am telling you Imren Tegin
is after us, Malhun Hatun!
Mother. They are not safe in anywhere but palace.
Ulgen, put alps on their door.
My Valide.
I can not leave Holofira.
-We can not put the enemy among us, Orhan.
-They will not leave the room, mother.
Our eyes will be on them.
Ulgen, take them to the visitors room.
Care! Osman Bey!
O, the soldiers of Kayi! O, the valiants of Kayi!
Some of your ancestors..
..became martyrs to turn these lands into home!
However, with Allah's permission,
we kept it as home, thank Allah
We grew it, with the power
Allah gave us, thank Allah!
And we always knew the words of
our fathers as the utmost important.
Do not forget this! Those who are
afraid of growing are bound to stay small!
That is why, we will never stop! We will march on!
We will be worthy of our spilled blood!
We will always endure the
swords that came in our way!
And with Allah's permission,
we will be victorious, I hope.
Now, our destination is Kite.
Of course they burnt down our preparations!
We will be wounded today,
however, do not forget this..
..do not forget that they will
never have what we have!
They will never have..
..our faith and our hearts!
O the valiants of Kayi!
Our courage will destroy their walls today!
If Allah permits!
-Allah is the greatest!
-Our holy fight shall be blessed!
-Yes, my Bey!
You've dragged Osman into a hole..
..by destroying the Kite encampment, Imren Tegin.
If he is clever, he would beg for forgiveness.
I've heard from an old wise man. The real
battle starts with the defeat of one side.
Osman must be ill-tempered now.
He must be waiting for a hope to strike.
He will find his hope among
his burning encampment.
You see the hope, when you
look at the eyes of your prey.
Stay cautious. He will try me.
Let us go and see what
Osman's tongue will spit out.
Near Atranos Castle
How did you know I would capture Kite?
I was sure you would besiege Atranos
for the vengeance of Bayindir Bey first?
I wanted this.
And you did it.
They praised you a lot. I thought the man
praised so much wouldn't act with anger.
You underestimated me.
I predicted your move.
You ran into rough weather this time.
Atranos' siege is just a distraction.
I knew your real target was Kite.
I played well and destroyed your headquarter.
You turned out not be worthy
of the praises, Osman Bey.
Atranos is still under siege. Tell me.
Who will save you from me now?
After your defeat in Kite,
...can you really take
this risk? I don't think so.
In Atranos, you will experience
what you experienced in Kite.
All of these castles will be mine forever.
Atranos is here. I'm here.
Come and get it, Osman Bey.
We never turn down..
...either our allies or enemies.
I will take both your castle...
...and your head personally.
Just wait for me.
-Come on!
-Move!
-Faster!
-Come on!
Come on.
Move!
There you come.
We will make you regret
that you came to our lands.
-Ya Haqq!
-Come on!
Come on!
Don't worry. Nobody will hurt you.
Our alps will take you to your homeland.
Where is your homeland?
You can either hear nor speak, huh?
Elcim Hatun, you are good at swords. Praise be!
Not better than you, Bala Hatun.
You know, Kayi women are as good as Kayi men.
Both at fighting and politics.
Who taught you to use the
sword so well, Elcim Hatun?
Mongolian threat, of course.
We didn't grow up in the palace, Orhan Bey.
In the east, you will pay for it with
your life if you don't use the sword well.
Bala Hatun, this woman is deaf
mute. She neither hears nor speaks.
This hatun can't find the
way. We shouldn't leave her be.
Of course we won't, Elcim Hatun.
-We'll make her settle in Yenisehir.
-Well said, Bala Hatun.
Otherwise, heathens will kill her.
Sisters, hatuns... You are alright, aren't you?
You are free now. Go to your lands.
Our alps and sisters will help you. Come on.
-Everything is set.
-Everybody should be very careful.
-We're going into the scorpion's nest.
-It won't be easy.
But we're ready to sacrifice our lives.
Tough fights will bring
great victories, Elcim Hatun.
Come on. We need to go.
They burned everything down. All
our preparations have gone for nothing.
But you will see.
Allah will give us a great victory.
You will see.
Bury our martyrs. Heal all the wounded ones.
How did the dog called Imren
Tegin find the headquarter, my Bey?
We have a traitor inside, obviously.
Obviously, someone tells him. Or
he couldn't have found this place.
But now that dog will think
we're going to march to Atranos.
Let him think so!
Gunduz Bey!
My alps are ready to fight, Osman Bey.
Thank you, live long.
On such a day they burned our everything down,
...your alps came just in time.
It's an honor to be fight with you, Osman Bey.
However tired my alps are,
...for the settlement of Turks
and the unity of Kayi people,
they will fight like a valiant if Allah permits.
Thank you. We can see our
friends only in difficult times.
You showed us that you are our friend.
Now... It is time for us to show our enmity.
You will see! With Allah's consent,
we will gain a glorious victory.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-If Allah permits.
I don't trust Olivia, Ulgen. Keep your
eyes on them. They won't talk to anyone.
You will watch them. If they
make a move, we will catch them.
I won't even blink, Malhun Hatun. I know my duty.
Is Imren Tegin bringing his
own men to break the siege?
That's what Olivia Hatun says. It
aligns with what my Orhan said but..
...I don't know if they are playing
a game or telling the truth, my Bey.
We will understand, we
will. But I am seeing that...
...Holofira is confusing you.
Their arrival, seeking refuge from us...
...seems as if they're here to use Orhan's love.
I am not comfortable with this at all, Osman.
If it weren't for Orhan,
I would never allow such a thing.
Learn how they got out of the
castle. Keep your eyes on them.
We will know every step they
take. They won't talk to anyone.
If there is a game, we will also find that out.
Holofira... Can we come in, my daughter?
Come in, Malhun Hatun.
So it was in our destiny to see
you wearing our clothes, huh?
Anything can happen in our lives, Malhun Hatun.
Everything can be destroyed in one night.
Right. Right, but...
...not everyone can get out of...
...a besieged castle, Olivia Hatun.
That's why I am confused.
So that Imren Tegin was going to kill you...
...how could you escape from
the castle when you were alone?
I ruled that castle for so many years.
I have a loyal commander. He helped me.
There's a gap where we piled up the
castle's garbage, and we escaped from there.
Otherwise, only our dead bodies
would have come out from the castle gate.
Wouldn't you become allies? Didn't you...
...invite the executioner of
Byzantium to cause difficulties for us?
Holofira? I guess that's what you said to Orhan.
Yes. I told him.
My aunt invited him.
Why would that man want to kill you?
He is at the frontiers thanks to you.
Imren Tegin is a demon. I made a mistake.
I invited our own executioner with my own hands.
You were lucky. You were able to
wake up from your sleep of carelessness...
...before your executioner strangled you.
I want to forget what happened in the past
and make an agreement with Osman Bey.
Osman Bey was always honest,
even when he was our enemy.
you allow me.
You came in such a time that...
...I hope you won't let me down, Holofira.
It's strange, right? You..
...are going to surround my castle,
and I am taking shelter in your house.
This is also your house, Holofira.
Everywhere I am is your home.
I have nowhere else to go but you.
Holofira...
You are the only owner of
my heart, Lord's daughter.
Whatever you see, whatever you hear...
...don't you forget this. My heart belongs to you.
We brought the prisoners! Open the doors!
It is too narrow. Let's take the
Hatuns behind us. Come on.
You seem too calm,
Orhan Bey. Holofira is not
in the castle, is that
why you are so relieved?
You can never be a prisoner
Elcim Hatun. Your mind and tongue...
...are as sharp as your sword.
-You should know that.
I will never be a
prisoner, and I will never
bow down. Think about
that marriage issue again.
Alright! Go on!
Go on!
-You were late.
-They were angry.
It was hard to control them, but we did it.
Which way did you use?
We don't know these lands very well.
They said, "Head towards the west."
That's how we found the castle.
We sent you a letter.
Everything was written there.
Show me the letter.
-Come on!
-Ya Allah!
Come on Sisters!
Allah is the Greatest!
Come on!
Hold the doors! Close the doors!
The doors!
I am going there!
Elcim Hatun!
Come on Alps!
Attack, for Bayindir Bey!
Hold the doors!
-This door is the door of gaza!
This door won't be closed!
The valiants are on the battlefield! They will
fall and we will win! Allah is the Greatest!
Alps! Kite Castle is now ours! Attack!
Bala, you are alright, right?
-I am, Osman Bey.
I missed fighting next to you!
-I missed that as well!
Look at them. What do you see, huh?
I see us, Osman Bey. I see
our youth. But we were faster.
Come on, Osman Bey.
-We are still fast!
The commander of these coward
dogs is running away! Inform Osman Bey!
My Bey, the Commander of
the Castle is running away!
He cannot go anywhere! Orhan! Take the castle!
Yes my Bey! Alps! Go everywhere!
Allah is the Greatest!
Where are you going, huh?
-I won't die alone here.
I will send you alone.
But don't worry. You
won't stay alone there for
a long time. I will send
the others after you.
Now, you will tell me about Imren Tegin's move.
If you tell the truth, I will spare your life.
Alright, stop.
As you say, there are infidels coming in crowds.
They were going to gather at Kite,
but they will gather in front of Kite now.
You have no escape, Osman. That army will..
..destroy you and the siege of Atranos.
We are the only one here who keep their words.
However, you are the ones being dogs.
Praise be! Thank you my Creator!
Thank you my Creator!
O the indomitable heart!
The sturdy hands! Soldiers
of Kayi, valiants of Kayi!
Hatlins of Kayi, we have
defeated the infidels thank Allah!
Thank Allah!
-We destroyed them thanks to Allah!
-Thank Allah!
We believed, we went for it!
Do not forget! Destiny loves effort!
That is why my Creator has..
..granted us Castle Kite.
Everyone contributed for it!
However, know this well.
We are guests here.
Castle Kite belongs to Gunduz Bey from now on.
Osman Bey, you help a swordless man..
..you feed the hungry, you
give the homeless a home..
..your troubles, your cause is one with us.
From now on, know that..
..the target you point will be the target
of my alps and my arrowsi may you prevail!
May you prevail.
Alps! Valiants, Hatuns!
For the World Order, for the great cause.
..are you with me..
..to fight with me until death?
-We are with you!
-Are you with me?
-Allah is the greatest!
Tisimus.
You will stay here. You
will wait for the distraction..
-..I will cause at night to escape.
-What will you do?
I will kill Osman.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
-Brother?
-Does your wound hurt, sister?
No. It comes and goes time to time.
Your life is more important than
everyone else my Gonca, do not forget this.
You will not lunge in front of anyone from now on.
-Are we allowed, my Shahzade?
-Come in Cerkutay.
My Shahzade. Osman Bey sends word.
He announced the conquest of Kite.
Osman Bey used Atranos as the bait, huh?
Good move, huh, Cerkutay?
Osman Bey invites you and Gonca Hatun...
...to the victory dinner in Kite.
Alright then. Let's go share
Osman Bey's victory, huh?
Come on. Prepare the horses, Cerkutay.
Nightingales are singing with grief.
Maybe it's its grief that
makes the sound so beautiful.
Just like it's grief that matures
and completes a human,
...nightingale's beautiful
voice is hidden in its grief.
Your grief doesn't seem
less than the nightingale's.
It has a matter with the rose.
What is the matter with you?
My matter is not knowing.
Not knowing the secret in Gonca.
Is it this important to know?
I was deceived, Dervish.
I thought the thing on the
rosebud was the pure dewdrop,
...but it turned out to be
coal tar, covering my love.
But I don't know why she
covered my love with coal tar.
With whose eyes do you look at the rosebud?
You see the coal tar but do you see Layla in her?
I can't know more than how she seems to me.
Do you know Caliph Harun al-Rashid?
He got curious about Layla who made Kays fall
in love and got her brought to his presence.
Layla just felt shy and kept silent.
Harun al-Rashid looked at her face for long.
And he couldn't find the reason why Kays
fell in love. So he wanted to make her speak.
He thought she might smile and
he could see the beauty in her face.
She turned his eyes to Layla
and asked "Are you Layla?"
"Yes", Layla said. "I'm
Layla, but you aren't Majnun.
"You're looking at me with the
eyes with which you look at others.
"If you don't look with Majnun's
eyes, you can't see Layla in me.'
How does Majnun look? With wisdom and love.
Those looking with love see
Layla. Those seeing Layla...
...will see Allah. Can those who can't see
Allah can believe Allah is the Only God?
-They can't.
Remember. What makes people
believe Allah is the Only God...
...isn't knowing but love.
Eyes not looking with love will mean
nothing whether they know or not.
They are always blind and can only see the flaws.
Now you need to get rid of this blindness.
-For your information.
-Well, Shahzade Alaaddin...
You drew swords against
heathens and knocked them over.
What about your mind? Can you
swing sword against your mind?
Can you look with the eyes of Majnun?
I destroyed his alps and siege
weapons. I had finished him!
He hit me with my weapon. Fools!
Castles and lands can be lost with a noble fight.
I won't dishonor my fate
with the failure of fools!
What now?
Osman got a stronger hand by capturing Kite.
But I will cut off his hand
before he even tastes it.
A Turk's enemy is a Turk! I'll ruin
him and start my sultanate for sure!
Welcome, Mehmed Bey. Gonca Hatun.
May your victory be blessed, Aladdin Bey.
-May it be holy.
-Let's go.
What's the matter, Elcim
Hatun. You look so thoughtful.
I was thinking about our
victory and Osman Bey's dream.
How would it feel to become a
martyr for such a great dream?
For this dream,
...two tribe have to get
united. You know that, right?
I know.
You think you're making
the hardest choice for this.
But that's not the case, Orhan Bey.
Marrying a man whose heart
is beating for someone else...
This is my test.
This unity overwhelms your love and my pride.
Elcim Hatun, I didn't want this.
I ignored my pride and accepted it.
Now it's up to you.
It's up to me now, huh? It's up to me.
Attention! Osman Bey!
-Selamun aleykum.
-Ve aleykum selam.
Welcome. Welcome.
May your conquest be blessed, Osman Bey.
Thank you. Thank you.
-May your conquest be blessed, Osman Bey!
-Thank you, beys.
Thank you. Sit down.
The castle of Kite is the first of our conquests.
After this, we will march to Atranos.
And if Allah permits, after we take Atranos,
...we will capture Bursa, Iznik and Geyve.
If Allah permits, we will take
one more step towards them.
Well... It was tough.
So tough.
But those who helped us in tough times...
...will certainly be rewarded.
Everybody hear this well!
The castle of Kite and the lands around it...
...belong to Gunduz Bey now.
Boran.
May Allah allow you to
rule with righteously, I hope.
-If Allah permits.
-Amen.
Come on now. In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
You may start, enjoy.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Mehmed Bey.
You kept your father's word..
..and stood behind us. May you prevail.
From now on, we will not distinguish you.
Thank you.
My daughter Gonca. You
saved my son Alaeddin's life.
May you prevail. That is why, from now on..
..I will see you as my daughter.
Everyone shall know as such.
Anyone would've done the same, Osman Bey.
You can not put a price on life, my daughter.
No one would've done the same.
We owe you a life.
My Gonca is courageous.
She did what needed to be done.
That is why we stood behind you.
What make us prevail
against the enemy, is the heart.
Whenever you call for war, Garmiyanid Mehmed Bey
will be by your side always.
Thank you.
Come on then.
Send word to Cerkutay. I forgive him.
He can be with us if he wants or
stay on his duty by Garmiyanids.
Now it is time for Solgur Aga.
-My Bey.
-Solgur Aga.
Your contribution in the conquest is big,
that is why your share will be big also.
You will make new outposts at the borders.
You will control every caravan and those who pass.
I am honor to have this duty,
my Bey. As you command.
May you prevail.
Health to your hands, Malhun
Hatun. We became a burden to you.
Astaghfurillah.
You are welcomed.
As long as we are friends, that is.
Malhun Hatun. As a token of our friendship..
..I wrote a letter to The Emperor.
If you can send it..
..he will see Imren Tegin's true side and help us.
Because Osman Bey won't be able
to defeat Imren Tegin when he is alone.
You are very considerate, Olivia. But don't worry.
Osman Bey will defeat Imren soon.
Mother! I have good news!
I brought news from Osman Bey!
Kite is now the property of Kayi!
Thanks to my Allah!
The properties are taken.
The duties are given.
Boran... -My Bey...
Play your qopuz.
Yes my Bey.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
When he reached the age of twenty...
...he received good news in his blessed dream.
Against the tyrants...
...he is the hidden giant, Osman Bey.
He carries the blood of Edebal
...to bring pain upon the heathens.
He is the pride of Ertugrul Ghazi...
...he is a warrior like no other, Osman Bey.
He made such enemies kneel..
He rode the horses under the open skies...
...and struck down the armies of tyrants.
He is a black wolf, Osman Bey.
He struck down the armies of tyrants.
With the grey maned horses..
With good armor and sharp swords...
With warriors and brave hearts...
...he wrote an epic, Osman Bey.
When the poor people cried out in pain...
He shook the earth with his call...
...to from a state...
...and become a home for the innocent.
He made such enemies kneel.
He rode the horses under the open skies...
...and struck down the armies of tyrants.
He is a black wolf, Osman Bey.
He struck down the armies of tyrants.
-Osman Bey!
Father! -Gunduz Bey
Take him! Ayaz! -Gunduz Bey!
Gunduz Bey! Gunduz Bey!
Alaeddin! Check his wound!
Check everywhere in the castle!
Burn every place if necessary!
I don't want a single crusader here! Go!
Bring warm water! Heat a sword, come on!
Gunduz Bey!
Give it to me.
Don't worry. You'll be alright.
Hang on! Hang on!
-Hang on!
-Allah lets us live...
...and Allah makes us die.
I am dying here now.
It is the decision of Allah... But...
...promise me, Osman Bey.
Tell me! -I don't..
..have a son.
For me to find peace..
...and for the well-being of the state and Kayi...
...for the sake of your
grandmother Hayme mother...
...allow Elcim
Hatun and your son..
...Shahzade Orhan...
...to get married. -Father...
Gunduz Bey, stop.. Wait...
You will see...
...the wedding of your daughter Elcim Hatun.
Your daughter Elcim Hatun...
...will marry Orhan for the union...
...of Kayis.
Hayme mother also wanted to unite
Kayi tribe's people who parted their ways.
-With Allah's consent, we will be able to do this.
-If Allah permits.
You will see it.
We will organize such a wedding that,
every Turkmen tribe will stand behind us!
But... you will also stand behind me.
You will fight with me! Don't worry...
...you will survive.
But....
We will not let anyone who
stands against us survive.
Visit turkision.com for more!